Guide to the Carl and Shelley Smith Mydans Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- November and December 2015 Acquisitions, 1935-2015; 31.06; (36 boxes)
  - Numbered notebooks, 1935-2000
    - Notebook 6 - Santo Tomas; POW notes; notes on Gripsholm, 1942-01-04-1943-12-31 (Box 179)
    - Notebook 7 - NY; Tule Lake, CA; Washington, D.C.; letters to Shelley from Italy, 1944-01-01-1944-04-15 (Box 179)
    - Notebook 8 - War in Italy and France, 1944-04-15-1944-10-23 (Box 179)
    - Notebook 9 - Philippines; Leyte campaign, 1944-10-22-1944-12-31 (Box 179)
    - Notebook 10 - Santo Tomas; retaking Luzon, 1945-01-01-1945-04-19 (Box 179)
    - Notebook 11 - Leyte; Luzon; Occupation of Japan, 1945-04-20-1945-09-09 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 12 - Occupation begins; Shanghai, NY., 1945-09-10-1946-01-07 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 13 - Bikini; the USA, 1946-01-08-1946-06-30 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 14 - NY; mostly Occupation years., 1946-07-01-1947-03-23 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 15 - Japan; Occupation years, 1947-03-24-1947-11-04 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 16 - Occupation years; War Crimes trial, 1947-11-05-1948-05-29 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 17 - Japan Occupation into Fall of China; Shanghai, 1948-05-30-1948-12-31 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 18 - Occupation years, 1949-01-01-1949-09-08 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 19 - Occupation and Taiwan period, 1949-09-09-1950-02-08 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 20 - Tokyo; Indochina; Hong Kong; NY., 1950-02-09-1950-06-19 (Box 180)
    - Notebook 21 - Korean War, 1950-06-20-1950-09-11 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 22 - Korean War, 1950-09-12-1950-11-23 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 23 - Korea; Stanford; Hawaii; Matadero Rd., 1950-11-24-1951-04-30 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 24 - U.S.A; Matadero Rd.; California, 1951-05-01-1951-11-30 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 25 - Matadero; Yucca Flats; Atomic tests; London; Copenhagen, 1951-12-01-1952-07-01 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 26 - Britain, 1952-07-02-1952-12-31 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 27 - Britain, 1953-01-01-1953-07-31 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 28 - Germany; Iran; Egypt; Britain, 1953-08-01-1953-12-31 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 29A - Britain, 1954-01-01-1954-07-31 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 29B - Britain, 1954-01-01-1954-05-01 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 30 - Britain, 1954-08-01-1954-12-31 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 31 - Britain; Stockholm; Rome; Norway, 1955-01-01-1955-06-30 (Box 181)
    - Notebook 32 - Britain; Europe, 1955-07-01-1955-12-31 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 33 - London; Nigeria; Britain; Stockholm; return to NY, 1956-01-01-1956-07-31 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 34 - U.S.A.; writing "More Than Meets the Eye", 1956-08-01-1956-11-30 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 35 - U.S.A. - on book leave, 1956-12-01-1957-08-31 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 36 - NY; finished book leave; disc surgery; Guatemala, 1957-09-01-1958-03-31 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 37 - NY, 1958-04-01-1958-09-30 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 38 - U.S.A. - writing book, 1958-10-01-1958-12-31 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 39 - U.S.A. - writing book, 1959-01-01-1959-06-30 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 40 - writing book; leave Moscow, 1959-07-01-1959-09-30 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 41 - NY; Moscow, 1959-10-01-1959-12-31 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 42 - Moscow to NY and return to Moscow, 1960-01-01-1960-02-29 (Box 182)
    - Notebook 43 - Moscow; Boston University - honorary degree, 1960-03-01-1960-06-30 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 44 - Moscow, 1960-07-01-1960-09-30 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 45 - Moscow, 1960-10-01-1960-12-31 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 46 - Boston; Moscow; San Francisco; Larchmont, 1961-01-01-1961-04-30 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 47 - Philippines; NY, 1961-05-01-1961-08-31 (Box 183)
    - Notebook "Moscow" - (mostly Shelley's): Seth and Misty in Moscow school; trip to Samarkland and Tashkent, circa 1959-1960 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 48 - NY; Greenland, 1961-09-01-1961-12 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 49 - NY; Cape Canaveral, 1962-01-01-1962-05-31 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 50 - Samoa; Papee Te; Pago Pago; Tahiti, 1962-06-01-1962-06-17 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 51 - Moorea; Cuban Missile Crisis; NY, 1962-07-18-1962-11-30 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 52 - Travel; West Indies; BMEWS (Ballistic Missile Early Warning System) story; DEW (Distant Early Warning) line; Yucatan, 1962-12-01-1963-02-28 (Box 183)
    - Notebook 53 - Tristan da Cunha, 1963-03-01-1963-06-30 (Box 184)
    - Notebook "Tristan da Cunha" - research notes, circa 1963 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 54 - the Balkans, 1963-07-01-1963-10-30 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 55- Kennedy shot; General MacArthur in hospital; Easter Island; Army chopper desert tracks, 1963-10-01-1964-07-31 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 56 - the Balkans; Sir Fitzroy Maclean; Guthrie; Muriel Spark; Lippman; Easter Island, 1964-08-01-1964-11-19 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 57 - Angel Falls; "Thomas" published, 1965-03-01-1965-12-31 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 58 - "The War Book", 1966-01-01-1966-12-31 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 59 - "The Violent Peace", 1967-01-01-1967-12-31 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 60 - Vietnam; refugee story; RFK story, 1968-01-01-1968-06-30 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 61 - Bikini story; Cocoa Beach, FL.; moon shot; leave for Tokyo, 1968-07-01-1968-12-31 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 62 - reassigned to Tokyo again, 1969-01-01-1969-04-30 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 63 - Japan, 1969-05-01-1969-12-31 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 64 - Japan; Singapore; Hong Kong, 1970-01-01-1970-06-30 (Box 184)
    - Notebook 65 - Malaysia; Thailand; Philippines; Hong Kong; Japan, 1970-07-01-1970-11-28 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 66 - Tokyo; Hong Kong; Singapore; Fiji; Tahiti; Stanford; Connecticut, 1971-01-01-1971-05-31 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 67 - Connecticut; Stanford commencement; Cape Cod; NY, 1971-06-01-1971-12-31 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 68 - NY; Stanford; Rosemary dies; Honolulu; Guam; Saipan; Louisiana, 1972-01-01-1972-06-30 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 69 - NY; Maine; Tokyo; Singapore, 1972-07-01-1972-12-31 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 70 - Singapore; Japan; Philippines; Sabah; POW return; Orangutans, 1973-01-01-1973-06-30 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 71 - Singapore; Indonesia; Bali; Hong Kong; Malaysia, 1973-07-01-1973-12-23 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 72 - Singapore; Malaysia; Vietnam, 1974-01-02-1974-06-26 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 73 - Singapore; Malaysia; Turtle story, 1974-07-07-1974-12-31 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 74 - Singapore (Fall of Saigon), 1975-01-01-1975-06-09 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 75 - Singapore; Malaysia rubber, 1975-05-01-1975-10-30 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 76 - Singapore; Egypt; Israel; London, 1975-11-01-1975-12-31 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 77 - U.S.A.; Hommocks; White House - Jimmy Carter, 1976-01-01-1976-06-30 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 78 - Democratic Convention; Plains, GA (Shelley's notes), 1976-07-01-1976-12-31 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 79 - Kissinger; Clare Booth Luce; Boy at the Met ("Tale of Two Williams"); Asia trip; Misty at Stanford, 1977-01-01-1977-06-30 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 80 - Misty graduates / passes Bar; Vasconcellos; Mrs. Macarthur; U2, 1977-07-01-1977-12-31 (Box 185)
    - Notebook 81 - negotiating China trip; editing exhibit; LIFE begins to publish again; Germany, 1978-01-01-1978-06-30 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 82 - China trip, 1978-07-01-1978-10-31 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 83 - China book, 1978-11-01-1978-12-31 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 84 - NY; Shelley finishes "Vermilion Bridge"; work on China book; Mexico, 1979-01-01-1979-06-30 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 85 - NY, 1979-07-01-1979-12-31 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 86 - NY, 1980-01-01-1980-06-30 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 87 - NY, 1980-07-02-1980-12-31 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 88 - NY; China; NY, 1981-01-01-1981-06-30 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 89 - NY; London; retrospective, 1981-07-01-1981-12-31 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 90 - NY; Korea, 1982-01-01-1982-06-30 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 91 - NY, 1982-07-01-1982-12-31 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 92 - Larchmont; San Francisco; Retrospective, 1983-01-01-1983-06-30 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 93 - Larchmont; Retrospective; Turkey, 1983-07-01-1983-12-31 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 94 - Larchmont; Retrospective, 1984-01-01-1984-04-30 (Box 186)
    - Notebook 95 - Larchmont; Retrospective and book; Martha's vineyard; John Hersey; Moscow (Billy Graham); Estonia; Seth to Moscow, 1984-05-01-1984-09-30 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 96- Larchmont; Retrospective and book, 1984-10-01-1984-12-30 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 97 - Larchmont; Retrospective and book (done); work on retrospective film, 1985-01-01-1985-06-30 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 98 - Larchmont; Retrospective; Texas (Amon Carter); Sacramento; Fallen Leaf Lake; Martha's Vineyard; Boston (B.U. show), 1985-07-01-1985-10-31 (Box 187)
      This notebook is misnumbered as Vol. 97.
    - Notebook 99 - Larchmont; planning ICP show, 1985-11-01-1985-12-31 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 100 - Larchmont; ICP show; Philippines; Sacramento; Honolulu; Gloucester, 1986-01-01-1986-04-30 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 101 - Gloucester; Larchmont; San Francisco; Sacramento; Saratoga; Martha's Vineyard, 1986-05-01-1986-09-30 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 102 - Larchmont; Tokyo; Yokohama, 1986-10-01-1986-12-31 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 103 - Larchmont; Sacramento; (Crocker Art Museum show); Honolulu (Marcos Shoot), 1987-01-01-1987-07-31 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 104 - Larchmont; memoir, 1987-08-02-1987-12-31 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 105 - Larchmont; memoir; Sacramento, 1988-01-01-1988-06-30 (Box 187)
    - Notebook 106 - Larchmont; memoir, 1988-07-01-1988-12-29 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 107 - Inaugural; medical problems; Judith very sick; Corley dies, 1989-01-01-1989-06-30 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 108 - Larchmont; memoir; Judith dies, 1989-07-01-1989-12-31 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 109 - National Geographic talk; memoir; Imelda in NYC, 1990-01-01-1990-07-31 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 110 - Eddie Adams; Sandy stroke; splitting logs, 1990-08-01-1990-12-31 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 111 - champagne birthday in office; Steamboat Springs talk, 1991-01-01-1991-07-29 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 112 - Perpignan; Japanese screen; Denver show; Vadim calls; San Francisco show, 1991-08-01-1991-12-31 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 113 - Annalee; Bill Schuman dies; ICP dinner; LA riots, 1992-01-01-1992-06-30 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 114 - Moscow; San Diego, 1992-06-01-1992-12-31 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 115 - Sandy dies; San Antonio symposium, 1993-01-01-1993-08-31 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 116 - memoir; computer trouble, 1993-09-01-1993-12-31 (Box 188)
    - Notebook 117 - Northridge quake; New England trip, 1994-01-01-1994-07-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 118 - Larchmont; memoir; Perpignan exhibit; Circle gallery, SoHo; Japan exhibition, 1994-08-01-1994-12-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 119 - Binswangers; Circle gallery, San Diego; Dimitri Kessel dies; Jeanne MacArthur; Denver, 1995-01-01-1995-04-30 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 120 - Costa Mesa show; Tokyo; Elsie dies, 1995-05-01-1995-09-30 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 121 - Seth in Bangkok; Eddie Adams; Tom Lambert dies, 1995-10-01-1995-12-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 122 - Larchmont; Circle gallery, San Francisco; Circle gallery, Toronto, 1996-01-01-1996-03-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 123 - Larchmont; NYC; Life gallery FSA photographs, 1996-04-01-1996-06-30 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 124 - photo mentor panel, 1996-07-01-1996-10-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 125 - NY; computer, 1996-11-01-1996-12-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 126 - Del Rey beach; Vadim killed; show in SoHo, 1997-01-01-1997-05-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 127 - move downstairs, 1997-06-01-1997-08-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 127 (second book) - contains two entries, 1997-06-30-1997-07-02 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 128 - Eddie Adams; San Diego, 1997-09-01-1997-12-31 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 129 - Larchmont; Santa Fe exhibit, 1998-01-01-1998-04-30 (Box 189)
    - Notebook 130 - Larchmont; University of Missouri, 1998-05-01-1998-12-31 (Box 190)
    - Notebook 131 - Larchmont, 1999-01-01-1999-10-18 (Box 190)
    - Notebook 131 (second book) - Larchmont, 1998-09-10-2000-05-16 (Box 190)
  - Other notebooks and personal papers, 1939-2015
    - Address book - "Mydans - Carb", circa 1980s-1990s (Box 191)
    - Address book - "O - Origional [sic]", circa 1980s-1990s (Box 191)
    - Two small notebooks, by Shelley Mydans, with 2015 note from daughter, circa 1941; 2015 (Box 191)
    - "Gertrude Stein's note to me. France 1944" - Carl Mydans (Box 191)
    - "Original penciled notes at Chapei", circa 1943 (Box 191)
    - "References - ringed books No. 1," binder, undated (Box 192)
      Contains a copy of "Carl's Summary of his Notebooks Vol. I, 2 through 23."
    - "References - ringed books No. 2," binder, undated (Box 192)
      Contains a copy of "Carl's Summary of his Notebooks Vol. II, 24 through 69."
    - "References - ringed books No. 3," binder, undated (Box 193)
      Contains a copy of "Carl's Summary of his Notebooks Vol. II, 70 through 91, including Moscow USSR (not numbered)."
    - "Carl Mydans - A - K," binder, undated (Box 193)
    - "Carl Mydans - L - Z," binder, undated (Box 194)
    - "Son, sky, sea, birds in sky, ducks in line over cloudy sea," contact print, undated (Box 195)
    - "No set number - Mydans," contact prints, circa 1964 (Box 195)
    - "Shelby's and my holiday trip to west coast by car," contact prints, 1939-06 (Box 195)
    - "Aircraft jets - B.O.A.C. jet passed in flight, Paris to NY," contact prints, 1960-05-21 (Box 195)
    - "Signs 1959 Canada - Niagara Falls Motel," contact prints, 1959-07 (Box 195)
    - "Time, Inc. - Alfred and Kathy Eisenstredt and Carl Mydans, Martha's Vineyard," contact prints., 1961-08 (Box 195)
    - "Bikini, Marshall Islands (before the atomic test)," contact sheets, 1946 (Box 195)
    - Outtakes Magazine, Issue two, Winter 1992 (Box 195)
    - Portrait photographs - "to the office to identify...", undated (Box 195)
    - Photograph of Eddie Adams, Shelley Mydans and Carl Mydans, by Mel Levine, circa 1990s (Box 195)
    - "Carl publications - notes of interest," magazines and clippings, 1983-1988 (Box 195)
    - Various photographs and manuscript material, 1922-1997; 3 folders (Box 195)
    - Clippings, magazines and publications regarding Carl Mydans' career, 1983-1997 (Box 195)
    - "Carl Mydans: Retrospective of photographs to open at the Amon Carter Museum," negatives, 1985 (Box 195)
    - Carl Mydans - birthday photographs, undated (Box 195)
    - Time - contact prints, slides and photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 195)
    - "Not life - edited for exhibit, '77," contact prints, circa 1947 (Box 195)
      Includes: cormorant fishing, Nagoya junk pile, Nagoya R.R. station, Mikomoto pearls, and Shelley Mydans.
    - "Life - Cuban Crisis," contact prints, 1962 (Box 195)
    - Various contact prints - "no set number", undated (Box 195)
    - Various magazines, clippings and various material, 1985-1994; 2 folders (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - The Violent Peace, layouts, circa 1968 (Box 197)
    - Carl Mydans - Return to Bikini and Kili, 1968 (Box 198)
    - Perpignan, 1991 (Box 198)
    - Perpignan, 1991 (Box 199 (Oversize))
    - Copies of panels of Time Inc. Exhibition of Texas and set No.1 pictures, undated (Box 199 (Oversize))
    - French medals - Perpignan, 1994 (Box 200)
    - French Medal of Honor - Perpignan, 1944, 1994 (Box 200)
    - Commende Majeure du Roussillon, certificate, 1994 (Box 201)
    - Commende Majeure du Roussillon, medal, 1994 (Box 201)
    - Commende Majeure du Roussillon, broken wax, 1994 (Box 201)
    - Missouri Honor Medal for Distinguished Service in Journalism [blue case], 1998 (Box 202)
    - Joseph A. Sprague Memorial Award, ring, [brown box], 1986 (Box 202)
    - Ordre des Arts et des Lettres, chevalier [white box], undated (Box 202)
    - Occupation of Japan - tentative layouts, text for first section, undated (Box 203)
    - Photocopies from "The Japanese Reischauer", "Japan", Life library, and "Rising sun"., undated (Box 203)
    - Occupation of Japan - tentative layouts - section 1: the end of war (4 spreads), undated (Box 204 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 3: Surrender (4 spreads), undated (Box 204 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 4: demilitarization (6 spreads), undated (Box 204 (Oversize))
    - Occupation of Japan - tentative layouts - section 5: war crimes trial (10 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 6: economic problems (11 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 7: SCAP reforms (6 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 8: political reactions (6 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 9: rebound, crackdown & cooperation (9 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 10: Hiroshima (4 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 11: Fukui earthquake (2 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Layouts - section 12: American impact (9 spreads), undated (Box 205 (Oversize))
    - Photocopies of Philippines, pre-War set, undated; 2 folders (Box 206)
    - Box labels: China book, 1978-08-1978-09 (Box 207)
    - "China book: China color conversions - 68 negatives (total 132 negatives), envelope no. 1 (1-2)", 1979-01 (Box 207)
    - "China book: China color conversions - 64 negatives (total 132 negatives), envelope no. 2 (1-2)", circa January 1, 1979 (Box 207)
    - "China book: 53 copy negatives of China color conversions - most of these used in time", 1978-08 (Box 207)
    - "China book: secondary, remade B&W conversion prints. - rejected prints", 1979-01 (Box 207)
    - "China book: conversions not chosen", 1978-08-1978-09 (Box 207)
    - "China book: Time color conversions of pictures that book will use in color", 1978-12-18 (Box 207)
    - "This is [sic] worn out address book, replaced by nearly identical book May 1985," address book, 1985-05 (Box 208)
    - "No.2 Japan," address book, undated (Box 208)
    - "Old addresses and data," address book, undated (Box 208)
    - "People met or involved in life stories," notebook, undated (Box 208)
    - Date book, 1999 (Box 208)
    - Date book, 2000 (Box 208)
    - Memo books, undated (Box 208)
      Contains six flip-front memo books, numbered 7 to 12.
    - Date book, 1984 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1985 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1986 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1986 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1987 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1988 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1989 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1990 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1960 (Box 209)
    - Date book - travel, 1950-1964 (Box 209)
    - "Old addresses", address book, undated (Box 209)
    - Camera - notebook, undated (Box 209)
    - "USSR talks," notebook, undated (Box 209)
    - "Camera data," notebook, 1990s (Box 209)
    - Overseas address book, 1985-06 (Box 209)
    - "Professional," notebook, undated (Box 209)
    - "Things Japanese and Asian," notebook, circa 1969-1973 (Box 209)
    - Address book, 1965 (Box 209)
    - Address book, circa 1998 (Box 209)
    - Date book, 1994-1995 (Box 209)
    - "Reference names extracted from daily ringed book...", 1988-07-14 (Box 210)
    - "Shelley," copy of address book, 1982-10-07 (Box 210)
    - Address book, circa 1970s (Box 210)
    - "Story suggestions & projects," notebook, undated (Box 210)
    - "Singapore," notebook, undated (Box 210)
    - "Old replaced address book", circa 1970s (Box 210)
    - "Addresses," address book, undated (Box 210)
    - Address book, 1992 (Box 210)
    - "Addresses," address book, circa 1960s (Box 210)
    - Address book, circa 1990s (Box 210)
    - Address book, 1991 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1995 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1998 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1999 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1993 (Box 210)
    - "Carl's daily diaries", 1984-1989 (Box 210)
      Contains six date books.
    - Date book, 1969 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1968 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1973 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1972 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1971 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1982 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1983 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1970 (Box 210)
    - Date book, 1978 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1981 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1990 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1991 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1992 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1964 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1966 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1974 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1967 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1965 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1975 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1976 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1979 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1977 (Box 211)
    - Date book, 1980 (Box 211)
    - Shelley Mydans address book, circa 1940 (Box 211)
    - Shelley Mydans address book, circa 1950s (Box 211)
    - Shelley Mydans date books, 1966-1970 (Box 211)
    - Shelley Mydans date books, 1971-1975 (Box 211)
    - Shelley Mydans date books, 1976-1980 (Box 211)
    - Shelley Mydans date books, 1981-1985 (Box 211)
    - Shelley Mydans date books, 1986-1990 (Box 211)
  - Slides, 1968
    - "Bikini," slides, 1968; 5 slide containers (Box 212)
    - "Bikini: Coconut Crabs," slides, 1968 (Box 212)
    - "Bikini: Eneu: Assembly Island," slides, 1968 (Box 212)
    - "Eneu Island, Bomb Assembly," slides, 1968 (Box 212)
    - "Bikini: Geiger Counter," slides, 1968 (Box 212)
    - "Return to Bikini: Geiger Counter," slides, 1968 (Box 212)
    - "Return to Bikini: General Scenes," slides, 1968 (Box 213)
    - "Return to Bikini: General," slides, 1968; 2 slide containers (Box 213)
    - "Kili: King Juda's Grave - Burial of 6 yr. old boy," slides, 1968 (Box 213)
    - "Kili: People," slides, 1968; 5 slide containers (Box 213)
    - "Kili: People," slides, 1968 (Box 214)
    - "Kili: Preparing the pig and the night party," slides, 1968 (Box 214)
    - "Kili: village scenes," slides, 1968 (Box 214)
    - "Kili: Visit on Bikini trip," slides, 1968; 2 slide containers (Box 214)